https://www.usscreeningsource.com/drug-and-alcohol-test/customer-service/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyCr0sby_adm1n2018-10-30T11:59:54-05:00
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. At U.S. Screening Source we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, U.S. Screening Source collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. U.S. Screening Source’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how U.S. Screening Source’s visitors use its website. From time to time, U.S. Screening Source may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
U.S. Screening Source also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. U.S. Screening Source only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to U.S. Screening Source’s websites choose to interact with U.S. Screening Source in ways that require U.S. Screening Source to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that U.S. Screening Source gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive U.S. Screening Source updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, U.S. Screening Source collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with U.S. Screening Source. U.S. Screening Source does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
U.S. Screening Source may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, U.S. Screening Source may monitor the most popular pages on the USScreeningSource.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. U.S. Screening Source may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, U.S. Screening Source does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
U.S. Screening Source discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on U.S. Screening Source’s behalf or to provide services available at U.S. Screening Source’s websites, and (ii) have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using U.S. Screening Source’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. U.S. Screening Source will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, U.S. Screening Source discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when U.S. Screening Source believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of U.S. Screening Source, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a U.S. Screening Source website and have supplied your email address, U.S. Screening Source may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with U.S. Screening Source and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. U.S. Screening Source takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. U.S. Screening Source uses cookies to help U.S. Screening Source identify and track visitors, their usage of the U.S. Screening Source website, and their website access preferences. U.S. Screening Source visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using U.S. Screening Source’s website, with the drawback that certain features of U.S. Screening Source’s website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If U.S. Screening Source or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that U.S. Screening Source goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that are transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer of U.S. Screening Source may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by U.S. Screening Source and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, U.S. Screening Source may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at U.S. Screening Source’s sole discretion. U.S. Screening Source encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Search Products
Search for:
Leave this field empty if you're human: Drug Testing Information and Advice
Lab Confirmation & MRO Services
Order Tracking
Contact Us
Blue Grass Drug Screen, Inc.
Address: P.O. Box 676 Pewee Valley, KY 40056
Phone: 1 (866) 323-7336
Email: customerservice@usscreeningsource.com
Office Hours: Mon - Fri / 9:00 AM - 5:00 PM EST
© Copyright 2017 U.S. Screening Source. All Rights Reserved.Web design by Crosby Interactive.
Oratect AOT-06 Saliva Drug Test Kit (25 Per Box)
Oratect HM-15 Saliva Drug Test
Oratect HM-15 Saliva Drug Test – 6 Panel Oral Mouth Swab – (25 Per Box)
T-Cube Saliva Mouth Swab Oral Drug Test
T-Cube 5 Panel Saliva Mouth Swab Drug Test
No THC T-Cube-5CO
T-Cube 5 Panel Oral Fluid Saliva Mouth Swab Drug Test ODOA-856EUO
T-Cube 7 Panel Oral Saliva Mouth Swab Drug Test T-Cube 7PCPB
Mouth Swab Drug Test – Saliva Drug Testing using Swab Drug Test
iScreen OFD Nicotine Test
Alcohol Tests
Alco-Screen Saliva Alcohol Test
AlcoScreen Saliva Alcohol Test (24 Per Box)
Alco-Screen 02 DOT Saliva Alcohol Test
AlcoScreen 02 DOT Alcohol Test (24 Tests Per Box)
AlcoMate Alcohol Test
Alcomate Premium AL7000F Kit
Alcomate Mouthpieces Alcohol Breathalyzer (Package of 50)
AlcoMate Prism Sensor Module
iScreen Breath Alcohol Test
iScreen Breath Alcohol Test
(25 tests)
Q.E.D A-150
QED A150 Saliva Alcohol Test (10 Tests Per Box)
Search for:
Free Shipping on Orders Over $75!
